[{"answer": " Well", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And if it isn't", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Home", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Home", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Who fired you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Poor Dad, does that still bother you", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "But it isn't bad weather now", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I know I left them there", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Maybe she has", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Do you realize that you're accusing me of ...", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " What if I did take them? I'm sick and tired of seeing you hand out thousands of dollars to that family of yours...", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " That's a fine thing to throw up to me after all I've been to you...", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I'll give it back to you ....  all I've got ....twent", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " But tonight is Christmas Eve", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He's never forgotten a promise to me.  I'm worried about him.  I know something's happened to him", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You know, we know each other", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Aren't you my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I don't know anything", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's it...  my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "That's it...  my friend", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Why don't you try him again", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " I'll tell you", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Of course.  What's an extension for", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What are you going to do", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " You wouldn't do that...  you wouldn't", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And her with that sparkler on her hand, and thirty dollars in her purse?  Looks to me like our friend my friend came to collect and ran into a little trouble", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " There's a lot of things they don't see in this place.  And you say you haven't seen him or heard from him in that time", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh, then you did hear from him", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Well, what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "That's all right.  Well, we'll be going", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Goodbye", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "All right, then.  I'll tell them", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " I don't believe it! You're lying", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Do I", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Don't kid yourself.  These are the good old days", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " I don't know", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "She... she fell over backwards", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "How do you do, Mr. my friend.  My name is Diamond. Come on in and have a drink", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "As a matte", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That's all swell.  Only you're peddling your fish in the wrong market. I've got nothing to do with it", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " How is my friend?  I didn't know he was out of stir", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What'd he think it was to you", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm asking you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Let's see.  Where's it from", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " I don't know", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " But Wynant", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Why don't you", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What about this Nunheim", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Did you know he was hanging around my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I can't help it.  You don't know....", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "You've got to get your mind off this", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Go", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I've got hunch.  I'm going down to look at that place's shop, I want to find out why it's closed", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "He went away lots of times when I knew him", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "How did you get in here", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You worked here", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "My soul, woman.  I give you three murders and you aren't satisfied", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " I did find him", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "What are you going to do", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " Yes", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " Now my friend, what's that got to do with it", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Got a nice evening dress", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " Got a nice evening dress", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " Now my friend, what's that got to do with it", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I've got a lulu", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Who do you think did it", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "my friend, my friend, my friend, my friend.....", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "I wish you'd tell me", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " Last night.  He came to see me at my apartment", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "He didn't say very much.  Wanted to know how I was and how the children were", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Why do you say that", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": " Let's see... where was I?  Oh, yes.  He went to find the man. That man was desperate!  He knew that he was caught dead to rights", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "He's been dead for three months", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "What did he pay you, my friend, to stick to that story", "docId": "thethinman.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You're lying, my friend.  But then, you'd do anything for money.  You're getting a good price for saying you saw Wynant and you figure you won't get anything if he's dead", "qsentId": 82}]